ucnews.in 2019-05-18

# UC News: Latest news India, Top India headlines, Breaking News from Indian states

### Privacy Policy

Clauses

Your privacy is important to us and this statement sets out the Privacy Policy and practices of UCWeb , its subsidiaries and associated companies (together, the “Group”, “We” or “Us”) that will be followed with respect to the collection, use and/or disclosure of users’ personal data in connection with its mobile application, UC News (“UC News”). Please do not use the UC News service if you do not agree with our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to our Terms of Service. Your use of UC News and any personal information you provide on UC News is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. This Privacy Policy complements, and does not limit or replace, the purposes for which you provide the Group with your personal data which may be expressly stated in any form for submission of personal data to the Group. 

#### 1\. Personal Data that We Collect, Use and/or Disclose

The types of data that UC News collects, uses and/or discloses includes, but is not limited to, information that is provided by you, your mobile phone device or social media platform. Some of this data may personally identify you.

When you download UC News, our equipment will automatically record:

(i) International Mobile Station Equipment (IMEI) number or similar device identification numbers;

(ii) the make, model and manufacturer of your device; and

(iii) the version of your operating system.

When you use UC News, our equipment will also automatically record some general information in addition to the abovementioned data, including:

(i) a list of mobile applications you have installed on your device

(ii) your Internet Protocol address;

We generally do not collect, use and/or disclose other personal data about you through your usage of UC News although your personal data will be made available to us should you choose to sync your social media platform with UC News. We may nevertheless disclose to third parties anonymized information generated from your usage of UC News.

2\. Purposes

You hereby agree that the Group may collect, store, process, disclose, access, review and/or use personal data (including sensitive personal data) about you, whether obtained from you or from other sources, for the purposes set out below and/or any other administrative or operational purposes and/or the purpose of managing your relationship as a user of UC News or as a customer with the Company or any other company within the Group:

(i) verification and identification purposes; 

(ii) enabling your use of the services which the Group or UC News provides, including, where necessary, contacting you (whether by in-app notifications via UC News, SMS, email or instant messaging services);

(iii) providing services to you in relation to your usage of UC News;

(iv) facilitating interoperability between other social media platforms (such as Facebook) and UC News;

(v) dealing with enquiries made by you;

(vi) providing software support and maintenance in connection with your usage of UC News;

(vii) troubleshooting and maintenance of our server(s);

(viii) maintenance and updating of the personal data; 

(ix) withholding tax from lucky draw winnings when you win our lucky draws;

(x) statistical analysis; 

(xi) understanding and analysing usage patterns;

(xii) administrative or operational purposes; 

(xiii) tax filing preparation;

(xiv) processing credit notes and processing refunds;

(xv) collection of fees, charges and expenses for services provided;

(xvi) facilitating the making and payment of claims, including payments by cheque, bank transfers or other means;

(xvii) carrying out billing, accounting, auditing and the maintenance of proper book-keeping to explain the Company’s operations and business;

(xviii) the disclosure of the relevant books, documents, records and information (in hard or soft copy) to the auditors for the preparation of financial reports; and/or

(xix) if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with the law or respond to a court order.

3\. Marketing & Optional Purposes

We invite you to receive marketing and promotional communications from us. If you wish to be updated about our latest developments, promotions, services and events, please allow in-app notifications via UC News so that we may notify and update you from time to time.

You may withdraw your consent to receive such marketing and promotional communications by selecting the applicable settings within UC News at any time.

Should you prefer not to receive any marketing or promotional communications from us, please note that we may still contact you for service-related purposes like customer research or for account administration reasons, such as customer service notifications, and to notify you of your winnings when you choose to participate in any of our lucky draws.

4\. Data Quality

You agree that all personal data you provide to us on accessing and/or using UC News is and shall remain accurate, complete and up to date. On our part, the Group will take reasonable steps to make sure that the personal data it collects, uses or discloses is accurate and complete.

5\. Data Security

The Group will take reasonable steps to protect the personal data it holds from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.

The Group will not keep personal data for longer than is necessary for business and/or legal purposes and will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal data if it is no longer needed.

6\. Transborder Data Flows 

If your personal data is transferred to a country or territory outside, for instance, if your personal data is required for administrative or operational purposes in other companies within the Group, we will ensure that the recipients thereof provide a standard of protection to your personal data so transferred that is comparable to that which is provided herein.

7\. Updates to the Privacy Policy

The Group will revise this Privacy Policy from time to time and the updated versions will be dated so that you are aware of any changes made. Your continued use of UC News constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any amendments. 

Subject to applicable laws, the English version of this Privacy Policy will prevail over any version of this Privacy Policy in another language. 

8\. Contact Us

You may write to us at [help@ucweb.com] for any privacy concerns and requests relating to this Privacy Policy, or our Product and Services.
